>> Kyle Simpson: 现在开始讨论范围实际上可以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now it start to talk
about the idea that scopes can actually be
嵌套在彼此之间。
nested inside of each other.
这样我们就能进一步的比喻了
So we're gonna even further
stretch that bucket metaphor.
现在我们说的是水桶旁边桶旁边的桶
Now we're talking about the bucket within
the side of a bucket within the side of
这桶太奇怪了
the bucket, it gets really weird.
但我们要把木桶都放下好吗
But we're gonna have buckets
all the way down, okay?
[ 笑声 ]
[LAUGH].
让我们像以前一样快速处理这个问题
So let's process this quickly exactly
the same way as we have before,
完全一样的规则好吗
same rules entirely, okay?
我们首先看第一条，那是哪种大理石?
We start by looking at line one,
that's a what kind of marble?
第一行是正式声明吗
Line one is a formal
declaration that makes a?
>> 类: 红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Class: Red marble.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 制作一个红色的大理石，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Makes a red marble,
right?
我们要制造一个红色的大理石
We're gonna create a red marble.
第三行是一个正式的声明，它创造了一个什么颜色的大理石?
Line three is a formal declaration
that creates a what color marble?
>> 类:Red。
&gt;&gt; Class: Red.
>> Kyle Simpson: 第四行是一个声明，用于创建一个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line four is
a declaration that creates a what
颜色大理石吗
color marble?
>> 类:Blue。
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 蓝色的大理石，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A blue marble, right?
现在我们在蓝色范围内
Now we're inside of the blue scope.
第 6 行是创建什么颜色模块的声明 ?
Line six is a declaration that
creates what color module?
>> 类:Blue。 >> Kyle Simpson: 蓝色模块，
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The blue module,
cubz 在别的课的范围内，对吧 ?
cuz ask is in the scope of
the other class, right?
函数声明使其标识在其外层作用域中，
Function declarations make their
identifier in their enclosing scope,
这很关键记住这一点
that's critical, keep that in mind.
好吧那我们就在里面问颜色范围是什么
All right, so then we're inside of ask and
it's made of what color scope?
>> Student: Yellow. >> 类: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Student: Yellow.
&gt;&gt; Class: [LAUGH]
>> Kyle Simpson: 当然，请将其更改为我们。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sure, change it up on us.
我们一直在使用绿色，但让我们切换到黄色。
We've been using green, but
let's switch to yellow.
别乱了
No confusion.
好的好的
[LAUGH] Okay,
如果我没说绿色的话我会说点错误的
I'm gonna stick with green cuz I'm gonna
say something wrong if I don't say green.
我们创造了一个绿色的范围。
We've created a green scope.
没有要创作的弹珠，但有对弹珠的引用。
There's no marbles to create, but
there are references to marbles.
所以当我们引用老师的时候
So on line seven when
we reference teacher,
那是什么样的大理石
what kind of marble is that gonna be?
第 7 行的老师是什么颜色的
What color marble is
the teacher on line 7?
>> 类: 蓝色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue marble.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 蓝色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Blue marble.
第 7 行的问题是什么颜色的大理石
And what color marble is
the question from line 7?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那是绿色的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's a green one.
>> 类: 这是蓝色，因为问题随附于函数询问。
&gt;&gt; Class: It's blue because
question comes with function ask.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那么问题是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
question is a variable inside of
功能要求的范围，对吧 ?
the scope of the function ask, right?
那是什么颜色的大理石
So what color marble would that have been?
>> 类: 绿色。
&gt;&gt; Class: Green.
>> Kyle Simpson: 是绿色的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Would've been green.
虽然那里没有一个 var
Even though it doesn't have a var there,
参数在该作用域中正式创建标识。
a parameter is formally creating
an identifier in that scope.
所以我们有一个老师是蓝色的大理石，问题是绿色的大理石。
So we'd have a teacher being a blue
marble and question being a green marble.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在我们有了一个范围，就在范围之内，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now we have a scope
and that's within the scope, and
在一个范围内
that's within a scope.
而且这个范围的解决方式，当我们问一个问题的时候基本上是
And that scope resolution by the way, when
we ask for a question is basically doing
那个处理的地方，哎，老师，你在这个问题的范围里是存在的吗 ?
that processing where it says, hey,
teacher, do you exist in the ask scope?
然后当我们不去外面的时候
And then, when it doesn't then
we go out to the outer scope and
我们是在那里找到的
we happened to find it there.
但如果我们没有我们就会继续下去
But if we didn't,
we would have go on and keep going, so
如果你真的想疯的话你可以去 50 层
you could go 50 levels deep if you
really wanna go crazy with it, okay?
那么问题的价值是什么 ?
So what is the value of question?
>> 类: 为什么?
&gt;&gt; Class: Why?
>> Kyle Simpson: 这是字符串，为什么?，因为在第 10 行上，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is the string,
Why?, because on line 10,
当我们执行第 10 行的时候
when we execute line 10.
我们有一个可能要查的价值
We have a value there which we
might have had to look up, but
在这件案子里是个字面上的问题
in this case it's a literal.
那条线又怎么了
And what happens to the string line?
>> 类: 它被传递- >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它被分配给
&gt;&gt; Class: It gets passed-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It gets assigned to
变量问题，因此
the variable question, so
在请求开始执行前执行第 10 行的执行。
that execution happens at line
10 before ask starts executing.
所以当我们询问我们发现的大理石时，它是绿色的大理石
So when we then ask for the marble that
we find, which is a green marble and
我们要求的是问题的价值是吗
we ask for the value of question, it is?
>> 类: 为什么?
&gt;&gt; Class: Why?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是引述，为什么?这是字符串，为什么?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's the quote,
Why?, it's the string, Why?.
>> Kyle Simpson: 第 14 行会发生什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's
gonna happen with line 14?
第 14 行如何执行?
How does line 14 execute?
>> 类: 将查找红色按钮。
&gt;&gt; Class: It's gonna look red button.
>> Student : 它未定义?
&gt;&gt; Student: It's undefined?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们需要像以前一样做同样的叙事，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We need to do
the same narrative as before,
别跳得出结论
don't jump to conclusions.
叙述的工作是怎样的呢 ?
How does the narrative work?
>> 类: 全局作用域。
&gt;&gt; Class: Global scope.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 全球范围，我有一个，什么样的参考?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey global scope,
I have a, what kind of reference?
>> 类: 源。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Class: A source.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A source reference for
一个 Identifier 代码询问，有没有听过，答案是什么 ?
an Identifier code ask,
ever heard of it and the answer is?
>> 类: 否。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那是什么错误呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Class: No.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what's the error?
>> 类: 引用请求。
&gt;&gt; Class: The reference ask.
>> Kyle Simpson: 参考请求，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The reference ask, okay?
即使是在节目中存在
Even though ask exist within the program,
它在我们目前所拥有的任何范围内都不存在
it doesn't exist in any scope that
we have access to at this moment.
因此，它是一个未声明的变量，与自动全局变量不同。
So it is therefore an undeclared
variable unlike the autoglobals,
因为我们不是严格的
because we're not in strict mode.
不像自动全球化，它会为您创建一个大理石。
Unlike autoglobals which go ahead and
create a marble for you.
如果您有一个源引用了未声明的变量，
If you have a source referenced
to a variable that is undeclared,
它总是会抛出 ReferenceError，好吗 ?
it always throws a ReferenceError, okay?
这就是为什么要了解目标引用和目标引用之间的差异的原因
That's why it's critical to understand the
difference between a target reference and
源引用。
a source reference.
至少如果你处于非严格模式
At least if you're in non-strict mode.
一旦进入严格模式，它们的行为都是一样的。
Once you go to strict mode,
they both behave exactly the same, so
它的目标与参考相比更重要
it stops mattering as much
target versus reference.
> > 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我们会在这里看到一个参考，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
we're gonna see a reference here,
在第 14 行出现 ReferenceError 。
ReferenceError here on line 14.
怎么了
Yes?
>> Student : 当我们通过字符串的时候
&gt;&gt; Student: When we're
passing the string why to ask
第 10 行 - >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的。
on line ten-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah.
> > Student : 在幕后有吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Student: Is there behind the scenes,
是 JavaScript 说的远远等于为什么在某个时候?
is JavaScript saying far question
equals why at some point?
>> Kyle Simpson: 排序，对对，排序。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sort of, yeah, sort of.
>> 学生: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Student: Okay.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我认为在概念上，它可以思考自变量
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think conceptually
it works to think about arguments
正在分配给参数。
being assigned to parameters.
严格来说这不是技术上的问题但它足够接近
It's not technically that, but
it's close enough that it works for
这一特别的叙述练习
this particular narrative exercise.